bi-lo.com 2019-05-31

# 

BI-LO is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers, and we pledge to protect the security and privacy of your personal information. By viewing this website (www.bi-lo.com), BI-LO’s mobile applications, BI-LO’s loyalty programs, or BI-LO’s social media (collectively, the “Digital Marketing Program”), you acknowledge our information collection, use, storage and disclosure practices (collectively, “Privacy Practices”) and consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “BI-LO ”, “we”, “our”, or “us” refers to BI-LO, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company, and includes all of our Affiliates (as defined below).

This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with BI-LO’s Terms of Use.

### Types of Information

You have no obligation to provide personal information to BI-LO. Use of the Digital Marketing Program, shopping at our stores, and participation in various BI-LO initiatives (including, without limitation, the Bonus Card program, promotions, surveys, polls, and sweepstakes), however, may require disclosure of personal information. The types of information you may provide to BI-LO include: (i) personally identifiable information (“PII”) and (ii) other nonidentifiable information (“Non-PII” and together with “PII”, “Customer Information”). PII is information that could reasonably be used to identify you, including, without limitation, your name, address, e-mail address(es), telephone number(s), birth date, financial information (including credit and debit card information), household information, demographic information, and photograph. Non-PII is information that does not identify you and may include statistical information concerning use of the Digital Marketing Program. 

### Use of Information

BI-LO may use Customer Information, or any part thereof, to: (i) complete and manage purchases, orders, returns, and exchanges; (ii) send promotional and marketing communications to you regarding BI-LO and its products and services; (iii) data share with our Affiliates and business partners; (iv) send coupons, mobile coupons, newsletters, e-mails, and mobile messages; (v) conduct research and analysis; (vi) administer contests and sweepstakes; (vii) create personalized content, offers, services, and advertising; (viii) prevent fraudulent transactions and theft; and (ix) comply with applicable law, governmental request, court order, or otherwise protect the rights, property, or safety of BI-LO or others. BI-LO may use Non-PII to analyze trends and track navigation within the Digital Marketing Program.

### Cookies

We may use cookies (a small, unique identifier text file), web beacons (a small graphic), and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Digital Marketing Program through your computer or your internet-enabled device. The purpose of this technology is to identify you when you visit the Digital Marketing Program so that we can enhance and customize your online experience. You may set your browser so that it does not accept cookies. You may also manually delete cookies from your computer. For more information on how to disable cookies, you should consult with the provider of your browser services. If you disable cookies, however, portions of the Digital Marketing Program may not function properly.

We may collect certain technical information from your computer or internet-enabled device when you visit our websites and other areas within our Digital Marketing Program, including, without limitation, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, browser type, and any referring website address. We use this information to enhance your experience during your visit to our websites and other areas within our Digital Marketing Program and for system administration, security, and troubleshooting purposes.

We may use third-party software to provide advertisements on the Digital Marketing Program, implement e-mail marketing campaigns, and manage other interactive marketing initiatives. 

### Social Media

The Digital Marketing Program may include social media features and widgets, including Facebook, Pinterest, and Twitter. Social media features and widgets are subject to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to read each social media company’s privacy policy before using the features or widgets. 

### Mobile Applications

Our mobile applications may collect certain information from you automatically, including, without limitation, the type of mobile device, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, and the location of your mobile device (provided that you give permission for the application of location services). You can stop the collection of information via your mobile device by uninstalling the mobile applications (or, to discontinue the location information only, you can adjust your permission settings in your mobile device).

### Pharmacy Records

BI-LO takes special precautions with your pharmacy records. See our Pharmacy Notice of Privacy Practices for additional information. 

### Privacy of Children

In an effort to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we ask that children under the age of thirteen (13) not provide any PII on the Digital Marketing Program. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) and you believe that your child has provided PII to BI-LO, please Contact Us. 

### Data Security

We maintain strict security protocols, including physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, to protect Customer Information. These protocols include compliance with federal law and regulations and the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or disclosure of your personal information. Although we strive to maintain data security, we do not guarantee or warrant its security. 

### In-Store Cameras

We use in-store cameras for security and operational purposes, such as tracking stock levels and measuring traffic patterns. 

### Links

The Digital Marketing Program may contain links to other websites that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked website. Any Customer Information you provide when accessing a third-party website is subject to that third-party’s privacy policy. We do not control the use of Customer Information that you provide to third-parties, and we assume no responsibility for your sharing information with them. 

### Opt-Out

If you do not wish to receive catalogs, coupons, and other promotional mail, promotional telephone calls or promotional e-mail, please Contact Us. 

We maintain strict security protocols, including physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, to protect Customer Information. These protocols include compliance with federal law and regulations and the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or disclosure of your personal information. Although we strive to maintain data security, we do not guarantee or warrant its security. 

### Updates to Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, technology, BI-LO’s Privacy Practices, or the features of the Digital Marketing Program. All modifications and updates shall be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Digital Marketing Program after we post an updated Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. You should review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of any changes. 

### BI-LO Affiliates

The term “Affiliates” shall mean all current or future companies or entities that now or that are in the future: (a) controlled by; (b) under common control with; or (c) controlling BI-LO, wherein “control” means possession directly or indirectly of the power to direct or cause the direction of management or policies of an entity through the ownership of at least fifty percent (50%) of the voting securities, by contract, or otherwise. 

### Contact Us

If you would like to communicate with BI-LO about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to Contact Us.

Customer Support 

PO Box B  
Jacksonville, FL 32203-0297 

Copyright © BI-LO, LLC. All rights reserved.
